Ryan Shepard PUNK009
People's Archive, MLK Library
Ryan Shepard Collection
1977-2006
People's Archive, MLK Library
Shepard, Ryan
PUNK009
3 Boxes
Punk rock music
- Series 1: Printed Material
  - Subseries 1: Fliers - Activism
    - Beehive Autonomous Collective, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Food Not Bombs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Positive Force, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Positive Force - Women's Festival, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Riot grrrl, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 2: Fliers - Concerts - DC Venues
    - 9:30 Club; 926 N St, NW, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - American Legion Post 8, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Black Cat; Bombay Delight, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Club Asylum; Club Heaven, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Club Nocturne, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - d.c. space, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - East Side, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Food for Thought, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Fort Reno; George Washington University, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Mountain Lodge (Georgetown), Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Nightbreed; Old Cambridge Baptist Church, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - St. Stephen's, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Sanctuary Theater; Wilson Center, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 3: Fliers - Miscellaneous
    - Washburn Hall; Episcopal Divinity School, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 4: Fliers - Miscellaneous
    - Kupid - The Secret Code Cipher, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Series 2: Audio Visual Material
  - Subseries 1: Cassettes
    - Awl by Hated (Label: Simple Machines), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Original release in 1992. Appears to be a later issue casette from 1995. Inside of the Casette is a business card for "Simple Machines" with a note to Ryan reading "Heres the classic --Cheers, Pat"
    - 12/87 by Fire Party, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Fire Party Could be the name of a mix-casette, and dated 12/87
    - Embassy Tapes 1990 to 1992 by Various, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Casette with recordings of various DC bands
    - Rat Trap by Ape House, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2: CDs
    - Fantastic Success by Measles Mumps Rubella (Label: Doubling Cube Records), 2006 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3: 7" Records
    - Red Herring by Antimony (Label: Dischord Records/Regulus), 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - New Radio by Bikini Kill (Label: Kill Rock Stars), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Peel Sessions by Bikini Kill, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      No label listed
    - May by Bratmobile/Veronica Lake (Label: Simple Machines Records), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - A New Goal by Circus Lupus/Trenchmouth (Label: Dischord Records), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - A Primer by Crownhate Ruin, The (Label: T.C. Ruin), 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Join Our Club... - Werewolves! by Cupid Car Club (Label: Kill Rock Stars), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Walking in my Sleep by Desiderata (Label: Dischord Records), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Double-O by Double-O (Label: Dischord Records / R and B Records), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Me And You by Egghunt (Label: Dischord Records), 1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 3 Songs by Fugazi (Label: Dischord Records), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Recorded and Copyright in 1989. Possibly released in 1990
    - Resurrection by Fury (Label: THD Records), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Included inside is a foldout paper with credits and images
    - Hoover Limited - 02 by Hoover (Label: Dischord Records / Hoover Limited ), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      split release as Hoover Limited ‎– 02
    - Sidecar Freddie / Cable by Hoover (Label: Dischord Records / Hoover Limited), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Two Headed Coin by Hoover/Lincoln (Label: Art Monk Construction), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      Inside, and insert is included with biographical information on Herbert C. Hoover and Abraham Lincoln
    - Tools and Chrome by Jawbox (Label: Dischord Records / Desoto), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      insert
    - Thanks by Lünchmeat/Mission Impossible (Label: Dischord Records / ‎Sammich Records ), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Salad Days by Minor Threat (Label: Dischord Records), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      Inner sleeve folds out photos of band members
    - Measles Mumps Rubella by Measles Mumps Rubella (Label: M'alady's), 2003 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      Included inside is (1) insert with information and lyrics and (1) small flier for a show in DC in May 2003 at Black Cat
    - Hearts/Cardiac Arrest by Nurses, The (Label: Round Raoul Records), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Incoming by Rain Like the Sound of Trains (Label: Spring), 1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Sea Tiger Theme Song by Sea Tiger (Label: Southern Records), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 777 by Sevens (Label: Tolotta Recording Co), Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - This Side by Sevens (Label: Dischord Records/Akashic Records), 1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Mersey Mersey Me by Slickee Boys (Label: Limp Records), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - How Did You Get There by Sorts, The (Label: Southern Records), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Bass by Soulside (Label: Dischord Records), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Good Girl by Suture (Label: Dischord Records/Decompiosition), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Flameproof Suit by Tsunami (Label: Simple Machines ), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      Includes insert with with band image and information
    - Fugitive Family by United Mutation (Label: DSI Records / Dischord Records), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      insert with lyrics
    - Wedge by Various Artists (Label: Simple Machines ), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      Insert sheet with band information and label promotional information
    - I Don't Care if You Go by Velocity Girl (Label: Slumberland Records), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - My Forgotten Favorite by Velocity Girl (Label: Slumberland Records), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      Insert sheet with Slumberland catalog
    - Condensed Flesh by Void (Label: Eye 95 Records), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      Clear Vinyl; promotional leaflet for band
    - Heavens Of Hell / Never Mind by White Boy (Label: Doodley Squat Records), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      Insert with lyrics and photos
    - I Could Puke / Disco Elephant by White Boy (Label: Doodley Squat), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Maybe It's Better by Whorl (Label: Slumberland Records), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      Insert with record information and label information
    - Mind Revolution by Whorl (Label: Slumberland Records), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Subseries 4: DVDs
    - Washington DC Ambassador Theater Psychedelic Dance Hall Reunion by Jeff Krulik, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      "over two hours of video...taped during DH Historical Studies Conference...what a great oral history!"
- Series 3: Objects
  - d.c. space t-shirt, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Temporary Box Number